ACTWU Publications 5619 PUBS
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Box: 2, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). v.74:no.11 (1988:Dec.). Item is in English;Spanish;French.
  - Item 11: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). v.74:no.1 (1988Jan.). Item is in English;Spanish;French.
  - Item 12: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). v.74:no.2 (1988:Feb.). Item is in English;Spanish;French.
- Box: 2, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). v.75:no.1 (1989:Feb.). Item is in English;Spanish;French.
  - Item 2: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). v.75:no.2 (1989:Mar.). Item is in English;Spanish;French.
  - Item 3: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). v.75:no.3 (1989:Apr.). Item is in English;Spanish;French.
  - Item 4: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). v.75:no.4 (1989:May). Item is in English;Spanish;French.
  - Item 5: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). v.75:no.5 (1989:June). Item is in English;Spanish;French.
  - Item 6: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). v.75:no.6 (1989:July/Aug.). Item is in English;Spanish;French.
  - Item 7: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). v.75:no.7 (1989:Sept.). Item is in English;Spanish;French.
  - Item 8: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). v.75:no.8 (1989:Oct.). Item is in English;Spanish;French.
  - Item 9: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). v.75:no.9 (1989:Nov.). Item is in English;Spanish;French.
  - Item 10: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). v.75:no.10 (1989:Dec.). Item is in English;Spanish;French.
- Box: 2, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). v.76:no.2 (1990:Jan./Feb.). Item is in English;Spanish;French.
  - Item 2: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). v.76:no.2 (1990:Jan./Feb.). Copy 2. Item is in English;Spanish;French.
  - Item 3: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). v.76:no.2 (1990:Mar.). Item is in English;Spanish;French.
  - Item 4: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). v.76:no.3 (1990:Apr.). Item is in English;Spanish;French.
  - Item 5: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). v.76:no.5 (1990:July/Aug.). Item is in English;Spanish;French.
  - Item 6: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). v.76:no.6 (1990:Sept.). Item is in English;Spanish;French.
  - Item 7: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). v.76:no.7 (1990:Oct.). Item is in English;Spanish;French.
- Box: 2, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). v.76:no.8 (1990:Nov./Dec.). Item is in English;Spanish;French.
  - Item 2: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). v.77:no.1 (1991:Jan./Feb.). Item is in English;Spanish;French.
  - Item 3: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). v.77:no.2 (1991:Mar./Apr.). Item is in English;Spanish;French.
  - Item 4: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). v.77:no.3 (1991:May/June). Item is in English;Spanish;French.
  - Item 5: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). v.77:no.4 (1991:July/Aug.). Item is in English;Spanish;French.
  - Item 6: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). v.77:no.5 (1991:Sept./Oct.). Item is in English;Spanish;French.
  - Item 7: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). v.77:no.6 (1991:Nov./Dec.). Item is in English;Spanish;French.
- Box: 2, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). v.78:no.1 (1992:Jan./Feb.). Item is in English;Spanish;French.
  - Item 2: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). v.78:no.2 (1992:Mar./Apr.). Item is in English;Spanish;French.
  - Item 3: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). v.78:no.4 (1992:July/Aug.). Item is in English;Spanish;French.
  - Item 4: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). v.78:no.5 (1992:Sept./Oct.). Item is in English;Spanish;French.
  - Item 5: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). v.78:no.6 (1992:Nov./Dec.). Item is in English;Spanish;French.
- Box: 2, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). v.79:no.1 (1993:Jan./Feb.). Item is in English;Spanish;French.
  - Item 2: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). v.79:no.2 (1993:Mar/Apr.). Item is in English;Spanish;French.
  - Item 3: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). v.79:no.3 (1993:May/June). Item is in English;Spanish;French.
  - Item 4: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). v.79:no.3 (1993:May/June). Copy 2. Item is in English;Spanish;French.
  - Item 5: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). v.79:no.4 (1993:July/Aug.). Item is in English;Spanish;French.
  - Item 6: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). v.79:no.5 (1993:Sept./Oct.). Item is in English;Spanish;French.
  - Item 7: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). v.79:no.6 (1993:Nov./Dec.). Item is in English;Spanish;French.
- Box: 2, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). v.80:no.1 (1994:Jan./Feb.). Item is in English;Spanish;French.
  - Item 2: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). v.80:no.1 (1994:Jan./Feb.). Copy 2. Item is in English;Spanish;French.
  - Item 3: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). v.80:no.2 (1994:Mar./Apr.). Item is in English;Spanish;French.
  - Item 4: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). v.80:no.2 (1994:Mar./Apr.). Copy 2. Item is in English;Spanish;French.
  - Item 5: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). v.80:no.3 (1994:Summer). Item is in English;Spanish;French.
  - Item 6: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). v.80:no.4 (1994:Fall). Item is in English;Spanish;French.
  - Item 7: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). v.80:no.4 (1994:Fall). Copy 2. Item is in English;Spanish;French.
  - Item 8: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). v.80:no.5 (1994:Winter). Item is in English;Spanish;French.
  - Item 9: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). v.80:no.5 (1994:Winter). Copy 2. Item is in English;Spanish;French.
- Box: 2, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). v.81:no.1 (1995:Spring). Item is in English;Spanish;French.
  - Item 2: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). v.81:no.2 (1995:Summer). Item is in English;Spanish;French.
  - Item 3: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). v.81:no.2 (1995:Summer). Copy 2. Item is in English;Spanish;French.
  - Item 4: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). v.81:no.2 (1995:Summer). Copy 3. Item is in English;Spanish;French.
- Box: 3, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: 50th Anniversary Convention. Resolutions., Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    By ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America). May 9-15, 1964. Item is in English.
- Box: 3, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Amalgamated Bank of New York. Statement of Condition., Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
    By ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America). December 31, 1961. Item is in English.
- Box: 3, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Amalgamated Health Centers: Biennial Report, 1954-1955, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
    By ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America). A Report On The Realization of a Dream. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Amalgamated Welfare Plan: Biennial Report, 1954-1955, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: The Sidney Hillman Foundation, Inc.: Biennial Report, 1954-1955, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Box: 3, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Clothing Industry Supervisory Training Program. Module 1: Managing People, Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
    By Hart Schaffner and Marx; JTR, Inc. Highlights. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Clothing Industry Supervisory Training Program. Module 1: Managing People, Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
    By Hart Schaffner and Marx; JTR, Inc. Highlights. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Clothing Industry Supervisory Training Program. Module 1: Managing People, Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
    By Hart Schaffner and Marx; JTR, Inc. Highlights. Copy 3. Item is in English.
- Box: 3, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The Development of a Statistical Quality Control Program for the Men's Tailored Clothing Industry, Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
    By Kurt Salmon Associates. July 11, 1980. Item is in English.
- Box: 3, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: The Development of Test Methods for Fused Textile Structures, Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
    By Trevor J. Little; Michael Mokriski; William B. Kessler. June 1980. Item is in English.
- Box: 3, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The Development of Test Methods for Fused Textile Structures, Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
    By Trevor J. Little; Michael Mokriski; William B. Kessler. June 1980. Copy 2. Item is in English.
- Box: 3, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: The Development of Test Methods for Fused Textile Structures, Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
    By Trevor J. Little; Michael Mokriski; William B. Kessler. June 1980. Copy 3. Item is in English.
- Box: 3, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Evaluation of a Proposed Dry-Cleaning Method for Fused Textile Structures: Phase II Final Report, Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
    By Trevor J. Little; Michael Mokriski; William B. Kessler. January 1981. Item is in English.
- Box: 3, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Evaluation of a Proposed Dry-Cleaning Method for Fused Textile Structures: Phase II Final Report, Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
    By Trevor J. Little; Michael Mokriski; William B. Kessler. January 1981. Copy 2. Item is in English.
- Box: 3, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Evaluation of a Proposed Dry-Cleaning Method for Fused Textile Structures: Phase II Final Report, Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    By Trevor J. Little; Michael Mokriski; William B. Kessler. January 1981. Copy 3. Item is in English.
- Box: 3, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Financial Statements, Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
    By ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America). 1960-1961. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Financial Statements, Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
    By ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America). 1960-1961. Copy 2. Item is in English.
- Box: 3, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Men's Tailored Clothing Study: Phase One Final Report, Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
    By Market Facts, Inc. June 22, 1982. Item is in English.
- Box: 3, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Men's Tailored Clothing Study: Phase One Final Report, Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
    By Market Facts, Inc. June 22, 1982. Copy 2. Item is in English.
- Box: 3, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Men's Tailored Clothing Industry Salesmen's Training Manual: Modules 5-8, Publication (Box 3, Folder 15)
    By Insight, Inc. Second Revised Edition, March 24, 1983. Item is in English.
- Box: 3, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Men's Tailored Clothing Industry Salesmen's Training Manual: Modules 5-8, Publication (Box 3, Folder 16)
    By Insight, Inc. Second Revised Edition, March 24, 1983. Copy 2. Item is in English.
- Box: 3, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: A New Member's Guide to the ACWA, Publication (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Box: 3, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Preliminary Statistics: Trainee Retention at Arreta Hall, Publication (Box 3, Folder 18)
    August 1979. Item is in English.
- Box: 3, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Preliminary Statistics: Trainee Retention at Arreta Hall, Publication (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Box: 3, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Preliminary Statistics: Trainee Retention at Seitchik, Publication (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Box: 3, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Preliminary Statistics: Trainee Retention at Seitchik, Publication (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Box: 3, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: A Proposal To Develop Methods For Improving Productivity of Tailored Clothing Industry Sales Representatives and Sales Managers, Publication (Box 3, Folder 22)
    By Forum Corporation. Submitted to Marvin Brander and William V. Poccia. Item is in English.
- Box: 3, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Proposal For a Market Study For the Men's Tailort Clothing Industry, Publication (Box 3, Folder 23)
    By Market Facts, Inc. October 2, 1981. Item is in English.
- Box: 3, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: A Proposal For Upgrading Skill Levels At the Manufacturer/Retailer Interface, Publication (Box 3, Folder 24)
    By Neal Cochran; Dan Tagliere. February 12, 1982. Item is in English.
- Box: 3, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Prototype Production Control System. Task A: Investigation and Analysis, Publication (Box 3, Folder 25)
    By Kurt Salmon Associates. Engagement Number 0450/2198. June 1980. Item is in English.
- Box: 3, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Prototype Production Control System. Task A: Investigation and Analysis, Publication (Box 3, Folder 26)
    By Kurt Salmon Associates. Engagement Number 0450/2198. June 1980. Copy 2. Item is in English.
- Box: 3, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Summary of the Study of Hiring, Retention, Training and Absenteeism Among Workers in the Tailored Clothing Industry, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
    By Elizabeth Allison. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Summary of the Study of Hiring, Retention, Training and Absenteeism Among Workers in the Tailored Clothing Industry, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
    By Elizabeth Allison. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Summary of the Study of Hiring, Retention, Training and Absenteeism Among Workers in the Tailored Clothing Industry, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
    By Elizabeth Allison. Copy 3. Item is in English.
- Box: 3, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Summary Report on Consumer Focus Group on Men's Tailored Clothing, Publication (Box 3, Folder 28)
    By Market Facts, Inc. April 7, 1982. Item is in English.
- Box: 3, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: A Training Concept Proposal, Publication (Box 3, Folder 29)
    By Neal Cochran; Dan Tagliere. October 1, 1981. Item is in English.
- Box: 3, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Twentieth Biennial Convention. General Executive Board Report, Publication (Box 3, Folder 30)
    By ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America). May 21-25, 1956. Item is in English.
- Box: 3, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Twenty-Third Biennial Convention. General Executive Board Report, Publication (Box 3, Folder 31)
    By ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America). May 14-18, 1962. Item is in English.
- Box: 3, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Sing Amalgamated, Publication (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Box: 3, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: The Book of the Amalgamated in New York, Publication (Box 3, Folder 33)
    By J. B. S. Hardman. Presented to the Twenty-Fifth Anniversary Convention. Item is in English.
- Box: 3, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Celebrating the First Sixty Years: Amalgamated Bank of New York, Publication (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Box: 3, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Sidney Hillman: Labor Statesman, A Story in Pictures and Text of the Man and the Amalgamated, Publication (Box 3, Folder 35)
    By J. B. S. Hardman; Len Giovannitti. Presented to the Sixteenth Biennial Convention. Item is in English.
- Box: 4, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Fortschritt, Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
    By ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America). v.2:no.1 (1917:Mar. 30) - v.3:no.52 (1918:Mar. 22). Bound volume. Very Brittle. Item is in Yiddish.
- Box: 4, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Fortschritt, Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Box: 5, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
    By Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union. Item is in English.
- Box: 5, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Garment Worker: Official Organ of the Garment Worker's Union, Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Box: 6, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Report of Proceedings of the First Constitutional Convention, Publication (Box 6, Folder 1)
    By Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees. Item is in English.
- Box: 6, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Report of Proceedings of the Merger Convention, Publication (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Box: 6, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Rise Gonna Rise: A Portrait of Southern Textile Workers, Publication (Box 6, Folder 3)
    By Mimi Conway. Item is in English.
- Box: 6, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Report and Audited Financial Statements, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
    By Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America. Item is in English.
- Box: 6, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Special Convention, Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Box: 6, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Financial Statements, Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Box: 6, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Thesis: The Wage Policies of the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, Publication (Box 6, Folder 7)
    By Robert Elias. Item is in English.
- Box: 6, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Convention Proceedings, Publication (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Box: 6, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Report and Proceedings, Publication (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Box: 7, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Documentary History of the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Box: 7, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Report and Proceedings, Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Box: 7, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Convention Proceedings, Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Box: 8, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Report and Proceedings, Publication (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Box: 8, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: General Executive Board Report, Publication (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Box: 8, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Convention Reports and Proceedings, Publication (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Box: 9, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: General Executive Board Report, Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Box: 9, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Biennial Convention, Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Box: 10, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the 29th Biennial Convention, Publication (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Box: 10, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the 29th Biennial Convention, Publication (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Box: 10, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The clothing workers of Chicago, Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Box: 10, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Partners in Prevention: Health & Safety Action Manual for Local Unions, Publication (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Box: 10, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Amalgamated Panorama, Publication (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Box: 10, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Selected Bibliography of the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, Publication (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Box: 10, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Bread and Roses, Publication (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Box: 11, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: A Commitment to Progress: The Fream Continues ACTWU 1972-1997, Publication (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Box: 11, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Constitution, Publication (Box 11, Folder 2)
    By Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union (ACTWU). Item is in English.
- Box: 11, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Daily Dozen, Publication (Box 11, Folder 3)
    By ACTWU Local 496. Spring-Summer 1995. Item is in English.
- Box: 11, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 11, Folder 4)